

19/12/2001

ABOUT ME

Frontend Developer with over 4 years of experience in building dynamic and responsive user interfaces. Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript (ES6+), with solid knowledge of frameworks like React, Svelte, and Vue.js. Experienced in implementing best UX/UI practices and using preprocessors like SASS and build tools such as Webpack and Vite.

MORE INFORMATION

- Driver's license.
- Responsible.
- Total availability.

CONTACT



+1 (829) 559-6030



josemlopez1912@gmail.com



Calle fundacion #23 Residencial amanda I, Santo Domingo Este, Republica Dominicana

Jose Miguel Lopez

Mid Front End Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Support Technician TI

DIGESETT. | August 2021 - January 2023

- Computer repair technician
- Printer repair technician
- Help Desk

Front-End Developer

DIGESETT | January 2023 - January 2024

- Maintenance web pages.
- Web application developer.
- Systems analyst

Front-End Developer

Banco Popular | January 2024 - Present

- Development Apps.
- Management Database.
- Deploy Apps.

EDUCATION

Escuela nuestra señora del perpetuo socorro (FARD)

Primary studies | December 2019

INFOTEP

Technical studies | December 2019 - January 2020

Universidad tecnologica de santiago

University studies | August 2020 - Present

UDEMY

Technical studies | Present

LINKEDIN LEARNING

Technical studies | Present

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- SVELTE

- C#
- SQL
- .NET



19/12/2001

SOBRE MÍ

Desarrollador Frontend con más de 4 años de experiencia en la creación de interfaces de usuario dinámicas y responsivas. Experto en HTML5, CSS3, y JavaScript (ES6+), con un sólido conocimiento en frameworks como React, Svelte y Vue.js. Experiencia en la implementación de buenas prácticas de UX/UI y en el uso de preprocesadores como SASS y herramientas de construcción como Webpack y Vite.

MÁS INFORMACIÓN

- Licencia de conducir.
- Responsable.
- Disponibilidad total.

CONTACTO



+1 (829) 559-6030



josemlopez1912@gmail.com



Calle fundacion #23 Residencial amanda I, Santo Domingo Este, Republica Dominicana

Jose Miguel Lopez

Desarrollador Front-end Mid

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Tecnico en soportes TI

DIGESETT. | Agosto 2021 - Enero 2023

- Tecnico en reparacion de computadoras
- Tecnico en reparacion de impresoras
- HelpDesk

Desarrollador

DIGESETT | Enero 2023 - Actualidad

- Mantenimiento paginas web.
- Desarrollador de aplicativos web.
- Analista de sistemas

Front-End Developer

Banco Popular | January 2024 - Present

- Desarrollar aplicaciones altamente eficientes
- Manejo de base de datos
- Desplegar aplicaciones

EDUCACIÓN

Universidad tecnologica de santiago

Estudios universitarios | Agosto 2020 - Actualidad

Escuela nuestra señora del perpetuo socorro (FARD)

Estudios primarios | Diciembre 2019

INFOTEP

Estudios tecnicos | Diciembre 2019 - Enero 2020

UDEMY

Estudios técnicos | Actualidad

LINKEDIN LEARNING

Estudios técnicos | Actualidad

TECNOLOGIAS

- HTML
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- SVELTE

- C#
- .NET
- SQL